Blind auf dem Pedal
Another hand's on the wheel to take me down to paradise
Is this heaven or hell?
Or am I trying to reach for something that don't exist
Here we are
Going far
To save all that we love
If we give
All we've got
We will make it through
I know that I'm not who I want to be
I'm running on high hopes again
Make a change for the better now
Feeling high on life somehow
I know that one day I'll break free
Reboot my heart
Rewrite my name
失敗ミスだらけのルートも抱いて
Here we are
Never fall apart
君となら
何度でも start
Out with all the self-doubt
Do not kill that fear of thinking that I'll miss out
Sorry that I must go
I know that I'm not who I used to be
傷だらけの地図を
折りたたんでしまう前に
君の声の在処
座標に打ち込んだ
ありえない未来さえ
アップデートしていくなら
曖昧な “さよなら”
上書きしてしまえ
Make a change for this hopeless road
They don't want you to love me anymore now
I know that I'm not who I want to be
Now I'll break free
Reboot my heart
Rewrite my name
崩れそうな今日さえ連れて
Here we are
Stronger than the scars
君となら
何度でも start